http://www.weddingguide.com.au/privacy

You are hereHome » Privacy policy
Privacy PolicyYour Local Wedding Guide understands that you value your privacy and wish to
have your personal information kept secure. For these reasons, Your Local Wedding Guide places a high
priority on the security of information we hold. We have developed this policy to inform you of how
we manage your personal information and maintain its integrity and security.
We are bound by the Privacy Act 1988 and must comply with the National Privacy Principles. You can
find more information about the Privacy Act and the National Privacy Principles on the Federal
Privacy Commissioner’s website at  "http://www.privacy.gov.au/".
While we believe in keeping your personal information highly secure, we also believe that you have the
right to be informed about how we deal with that information so, if on reading this policy you are
unclear on any of the matters or simply want more information, please contact us on the email address provided below.
Collecting Personal Information
We aim to collect personal information only if it is relevant and necessary to providing the service or
product you have requested from Your Local Wedding Guide.
In general you can assume that we collect and hold the following information:
Purposes of Collection
We collect information primarily to send newsletters to you.
We may also use the information:
to invite you to expos hosted by Your Local Wedding Guide;
to inform you of developments at Your Local Wedding Guide and other services that we can provide.
We will not disclose information about you unless the disclosure:
is required by law;
is authorised by law; or
you have consented to our disclosing the information about you.
Securing Your Personal Information
We are committed to maintaining the security and confidentiality of the data you provide us and we will
take all reasonable precautions to protect your personal information from unauthorised disclosure, use
or alteration.
Accessing Your Personal Information
You have a limited right to access all personal information that we hold about you. In limited
circumstances, we may refuse your request to access, in which case, we will give you a reason for that
refusal.
We are not required to provide access where:
denying access is required or authorised by law; or
providing access would be unlawful.
Changes to this Statement
This Privacy Policy is not a static document; we may make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to
time for any reason. We will publish these changes on our website.
Contacting Us
If you would like further information regarding this Privacy Policy, if you have concerns about the information that we currently hold about you, or any aspect of this Privacy Policy, please contact Your Local Wedding Guide at:
Email: enquiries@weddingguide.com.au
Web: www.weddingguide.com.au
CONTACT
Directory
CATEGORY LIST
Accommodation
Bomboniere
Bridesmaids
© Copyright 2000-2018 Your Local Wedding Guide. All rights reserved.
